KAIYI ZHU

Waterloo, ON · ky2zhu@uwaterloo.ca · (905) 587-0808 · kaiyizhu.com

Ambitious, performance-driven with many all-around skills and talents. Seeking to learn and experience various positions to continue the trend of being the jack of all trades, master of all.

Summary

Highly proficient in computer applications, with experience in many development tools and languages. Creative and analytical, with high attention to detail while maintaining both a positive and professional attitude. Strong ability to work well within a team and as an individual with minimal supervision.

EDUCATION

University of Waterloo

Waterloo, ON

Bachelor of Mathematics and Business Administration (Double-Degree)

Sep 2019 - Present

Work Experiences

TD Securities

Toronto, ON

Business Systems Analyst

January - April 2022

- Coordinated with multiple security development teams with weekly releases and created over 50 dev/pat/prod change orders on ServiceNow
- Constructed dashboards for higher visibility using Tableau and MS Excel data
- Translated and documented official business, technical reports for front and back office
- Ensured quality utilizing regression, functional and automated testing through VMs and Jenkins
- Demonstrated excellent project management and communication skills to procure and coordinate human resources

NetDynamic Consulting Inc.

Mississauga, ON

Developer

January 2021 - April 2021

- Created multiple custom SuiteScripts and implemented a system allowing administrators the option to view a pdf with audio features in NetSuite
- Programmed an excel macro for a client which allowed them to sort financial data efficiently
- Documented company's new Applicant Tracking System software integration with NetSuite
- Maintained company website using Elementor and WordPress

Deloitte Toronto, ON

Consulting Analyst

August 2020 - October 2020

- Participated in a 3 month virtual work experience placement through York University's Asian Business Management Program
- Conducted research on the impact of people, technology, process, while recommending high level IT solutions to current trends
- Strong interpersonal skills were critical to success in working with 15 other team members to develop recommendations to identify emerging priorities on the government citizen and social servicing in a post-COVID world
- Used insights to identify opportunities to apply technology using AI, automation, and data science to address gaps in the technological industry

Nanjing Dongqi Intelligent Manufacturing Research Institute

Nanjing, Jiangsu July 2019 - August 2019

Software Developer

- Validated data entries and reports on applications via MySQL database
- Created test plans for enhancements and fixes on Java web applications
- Developed Java applications using Selenium framework for automation testing of web applications

Bee-nies Apparel

Newmarket, ON

Co-founder, Financial Analyst

October 2018 - June 2019

- Managed and analyzed company financial records using Excel
- Contacted and bartered with suppliers to outsource products from foreign countries
- \bullet Implemented a strategy exceeding initial sales goal and increased the return on investment in shares by 200% with over \$2500 in sales in the span of 3 months